Logan Reynolds

I always go above and beyond to ensure the job is done right the first time. I have had much education & experience in this field & have (415) 886-0145 done many projects in teams & alone, which gives me necessary expertise to accomplish the job.

Computer Scientist

(415) 886-0145 LoganReynoldsLWR@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Intern, Software Engr - Web/Mobile Dev - UX/UI Design - Data Sci - WP — StageIV.com — 2020 - PRESENT

- Experience with: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, WordPress, Google Analytics, & More
- Building, creating, & maintaining the website. Analyzing user requirements & then designing, building, and testing software
 applications that satisfy those requirements. Juggle multiple problems & projects using domain expertise, programming skills, &
 knowledge of mathematics & statistics to extract meaningful insights from data, both structured & unstructured.

Intern, Software Engr - Web/Mobile Dev - UX/UI Design - Data Sci — Dance4Healing.com — 2020 - PRESENT

- Experience with: AI, Express.js, Heroku, Node.js, Jade, MongoDB, Mongoose.js, Twilio, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Passport.js, Vimeo
 JS Player SDK, Bit Bucket, Git, Github, Browserify, Google Analytics, Google Web Fonts, CI/CD, Photoshop, Sketch, PNG, JPG,
 npm, yarn, Trello & More
- Continuous integration and continuous deployment of the website. Including aspects such as web design, web publishing, web
 programming, & database management. Creating a computer program or a set of programs to perform the different tasks that the
 business requires. Building economical software which is reliable & works efficiently on the real machines. Worked closely with
 business stakeholders to understand their goals & determine how data can be used to achieve those goals.

Software Engr - Web/Mobile/App Dev - UX/UI Design - Game Des/Dev - Data Sci - Freelance - 2019 - PRESENT

- Experience with: JavaScript, Node.js, MongoDB, MongoOse.js, Git, GitHub, HTML, CSS, AWS, PNG, JPG, Express.js, Photoshop, Sketch, Google Analytics, Google Web Fonts, npm, yarn & More
- Applied mathematical analysis & the principles of computer science in order to design & develop computer software. Use of engineering principles & programming languages to build software products, develop computer games, and run network control systems. Designed data modeling processes, created algorithms, & predictive models to extract the data the business needs, then help analyze the data and share insights.

UX/UI Design - Project Manager — Amazon KDP Publisher E-commerce — 2018 - PRESENT

- Experience with: HTML, Photoshop, Sketch, PNG, JPG, PDF, Docx, E-commerce, Amazon KDP, & More
- Orchestrated the publication of 10+ ebooks on Amazon including paper & Audible publication of books. Gave ideas & directed
 ghostwriters in realizing those ideas as published works. Designed eight covers. This involves the design of the entire process of
 acquiring and integrating the product, including aspects of branding, design, usability & function. Making interfaces in software or
 computerized devices with a focus on looks or style.

EDUCATION

$\textbf{Make School "Dominican University,"} \ SF, CA-\textit{CS Bachelor's Degree}-2022$

- Concentrations: Software Engr Web/Mobile/App Dev (Full-Stack) UI/UX Design Game Dev Data Sci AI/Machine Learning
- Skills: Python, JavaScript, Swift, Go, Flask, Django, Node.js, React.js, UIKit, CoreData, Foundation, NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Keras, TensorFlow, P5.js & More

Meda Mission Techies, SF, CA — Full Stack Bootcamp — 2020

- Concentrations: Software Engr Web/Mobile/App Dev (Full-Stack) UI/UX Design Data Sci
- Skills: JavaScript, Node.js, HTML, CSS, React.js, DOM, MongoDB, Mongoose, jQuery, Command Line/Terminal, Git, GitHub, Wireframing, Flexbox, & More

Code Tenderloin, SF, CA — Coding Bootcamp — 2019

- Concentrations: Software Engr Game Dev
- Skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS & More

Noisebridge, SF, CA — Software Engr - Game Des/Dev — 2019

- Concentrations: Software Engr Game Des/Dev Data Sci
- Skills: C#, Python, Unity, SQL, Garageband, MilkyTracker, & More

Code The Dream, Durham, NC — Coding Bootcamp — 2019

- Concentrations: Software Engr Web/Mobile/App Dev (Full-Stack) UI/UX Design Game Dev Data Sci
- Skills: JavaScript, Ruby, CSS, HTML, DOM, React.js, React Router, React Bootstrap, Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails ERB, Active Record, AWS, SQL, jQuery, Command Line/Terminal, Git, GitHub, Wireframing, Chrome Devtools, Flexbox, Responsive Design/Layouts, MediaElement.js, Website Optimization, Performance Optimization, Web Accessibility, AJAX, Async, Fetch API, & More

Linda, Treehouse, Code Cademy, Khan Academy, Udacity, & More, Online — Computer Science Studies

- Concentrations: Software Engr Web/Mobile/App (Full-Stack) UI/UX Design Game Des/Dev Data Sci
- Skills: Google Analytics, SEO, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, DOM, React.js, React Router, JSX, Chrome DevTools, Web Accessibility, Web Optimization, Performance Optimization, MediaElement.js, Bootstrap, React Bootstrap, Flexbox, Git, GitHub, SQL, Images, Wireframes, Adobe XD, balsamiq, Sketch, Command Shell/Terminal/Command-Line, C#, Express, REST API, HTTP/HTTPS, npm, Node.js, Responsive Design, Google Fonts, Async/Await, AJAX, jQuery, API, Fetch API, Now, Netlify, Google Maps, Math, Ruby, Communicating using Markdown, Uploading your project to GitHub, Introduction to GitHub, Continuous integration with CircleCI, & More

Diablo Valley College, PleasantHill, CA — UX/UI Design — 2014

- Concentrations: UX/UI Design Art Drawing ArtDM Web Design Math
- Skills: Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Adobe Creative Suite, HTML, Drawing, Math & More

KEY SKILLS

- Expert: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Command Line & Terminal, Google Fonts, DOM, Git, GitHub, Adobe Photoshop, Sketch, Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Muse, npm, yarn, Google AdSense, JSON, Local Storage, Wix, Go Daddy, WordPress, CI/CD, Wire Frames, JQuery, (PNG, JPG, JP2, TIFF, SVG, GIF, BMP, PDF & PSD images), Async/Await, HTTP/HTTPS Chrome Devtools, & Trello.
- Proficient: Node.js, P5.JS, Pug, AWS, Cloud 9, BitBucket, Heroku, Now, Netlify, Adobe Creative Cloud Suite, Google Analytics, Google Maps, Jade, Web Accessibility, Web Optimization, Web Accessibility, Performance Optimization, Flexbox, Responsive Design/Layouts, Adobe XD, balsamiq, React.js, JSX, React Bootstrap, React Router, & SQL.
- Novice: MediaElement.js, Popper.js, Express.js, Mongoose.js, Passport.js, Vimeo JS Player SDK, Python, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, Erb files, Active Record, C#, Unity, WebVTT, MongoDB, Phaser, GTW, AJAX, Fetch API, REST API, AI, Twilio, Browserify, SEO, & SASS.

PORTFOLIO/PROFILE

- LWRGitHub.GitHub.io
- GitHub.com/LWRGitHu
- Linkedin.com/in/Logan-R evnolds

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Software Engineering
- Full Stack Web/Mobile/Application Development
- User Experience/User Interface Design: 10+ years
- Game
- Design/Development
- Data Science